{
    "id": "048b99e1fdae4f099a50bc34253e36c7",
    "title": "Combine using infinitives",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "161f527cfe514f48b979bf740a76c2ba",
            "title": "Infinitives Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "The soup is ..................................... hot for me to drink.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "so",
                        "too"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The problem is ......................................... difficult for me to solve.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "so",
                        "very",
                        "too"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The grapes are .................................................. sour for us to eat.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "so",
                        "too",
                        "very"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Akbar propagated the Divine Religion ........................................... India.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "uniting",
                        "to unite",
                        "to uniting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He worked hard ................................................. the promotion.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "getting",
                        "to get"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He went to the city ............................................... work.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to find",
                        "finding"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The traveler sat down ................................................ some rest.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to get",
                        "getting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She opened her mouth ................................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to yell",
                        "yelling"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He picked up the gun .............................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "shooting",
                        "to shoot"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I called him ...............................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "speaking",
                        "to speak"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}